Well, I guess it could be that I just love myself way too much.
I don't like anything that labels you.
It's not my fault others aren't interested in individuality.
I see no point unless you're wanted.
There's no reason to it.
Other than being wanted.
It just feels so good.
Akane?
Huh?
Hey Akane.
You dropped this.
I've always been like this.
This guy here, he was my friend's big school crush at the time.
I thought they would make a good match.
But what was it?
There was something.
Something about how neatly that would fit.
That really bothered me somehow.
Oh, sorry.
I'm a bit out of it today.
Honestly, I wasn't even interested in Saito in that way.
But maybe I was interested in the attention Saito was receiving.
I couldn't help myself.
I had to try.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for running off all of a sudden.
I was just really surprised.
You two just look so good together.
It's fine.
I'm good.
I hope that we're still friends.
If that's okay, I'd like that.
At that moment, the feeling I was getting was something new.
It wasn't really guilt.
Nor was it a sense of superiority either.
What I thought was, I would rather die than be in a position where I felt exploited.
Like she was.
I suppose that was it.
The day I realized I enjoyed exploiting people.
And what's so wrong with me loving that?
I'm just jealous.
Being able to love someone other than yourself?
That's something I can't imagine.
Akane.
Hey, are you awake?
Hey, Terauchi.
What happened to that girlfriend of yours?
Huh?
We broke up a long time ago.
You jealous or something?
Then that means there isn't anybody out there who can prove that this person is someone to be desired.
Hey, baby.
If you're awake already.
What?
Come on.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
No.
I'm...
Suddenly over this.
I can't really tell how good someone is.
Unless someone else says that they are.
Oh, she's looking again
Poor silly girl
She must really love him
Uh, um, Miss Minagawa?
Are you free after school today?
Please, I don't need much time
I just thought maybe we could go to a cafe and talk
This is it
I'm sorry, Mr. Kanai
I have some work I really need to get finished by today
Oh, I see
Then we can do it in a...
But, how about if we talk in the music room after school later today?
No, it has to be today
Miss Minagawa
Because
You had the audacity to come to me
Hanabi
Yasuraoka
The
is the guy you were with last night your boyfriend or something
oh no he was just a friend
if only that was remotely true right miss hannabe you know
miss hannabe yasaroka you just haven't realized yet that you belong on this side
haven't realized no no she's just trying not to notice right now
of course i'd be curious when someone like you would finally let your guard down and i could see
and now i have found your beloved mr kanai oh miss miss minigawa
oh hello there miss hannabe in the end this is really all your fault uh is there something you
need i mean honestly girl oh sorry you only have yourself to blame is this yours
mr kanai isn't my type at all
oh too bad i wanted to see the hurt expression on your sweet face
so let me see more
i need more more come on show me your pain
is something wrong
oh no class is starting
oh miss hannabe let's talk in the music room after school today
oh i just can't wait it's almost too much i can't wait to see that look of devastation
on your face
love or hate
it's never been my thing
i'm not one for strong emotions either way
i'm really pretty ordinary people like me we're just so boring
maybe it's my childhood my mother passed away a long time ago when i was young
if she were alive she'd be proud i'm a teacher
but as my memory of her fades over time
but the only thing i recall is her long thick hair yes like that just like that
love at first sight on a spring day
maybe i'm that simple and that's all it took
oh a cherry blossom
i think we saw each other this morning
what
oh well i guess you didn't notice me there did you
i saw you later on at the assembly
new teachers must stick together
don't you think
she's really too good to be true
but that's exactly why
may i ask what is your name
akane minakawa
i decided to believe it was fate
oh mr kanai
i'm sorry for being so late
there we go
it sure is hot
you said you had something you wanted to say
here it goes
i should get everything off my chest
after all
it's better than never saying anything
but i need courage
i'm in love with you
i need a wrestled
so she doesn't feel like she can be
in love with you
so
i wanted to learn
so i wanted to know
but it was great
that it was an spooky
The tears aren't coming.
Well, of course.
Why would they?
I have no right to cry.
Because I...
Brother is so amazing, putting himself out there.
I wonder if they're going to start dating.
I hope not.
That would hurt too much, having to see them every day.
I mean, I knew about it.
I always knew.
I know it's too late, but why did I have to hear it?
Though I guess I would have eventually found out.
So why didn't I say anything?
We've been together all this time.
Maybe that's why I didn't.
I was too scared.
Scared that maybe...
He wouldn't want...
To be my brother anymore.
Pathetic.
That's why you ended up losing him in the first place.
I'm sure Mugi would be devastated if he found out.
But he'll hear about it eventually.
No.
I should leave him be.
I would just be using him.
Hurting Mugi for my own convenience.
That isn't a good enough reason to go running into his arms.
Just how much have I been spoiled?
I need to rely on myself for once.
You're not going to movies today?
Sinai.
Did you follow me?
Huh?
Uh...
Yeah.
I did.
Is that weird?
Why?
Why do you...
How could you possibly like me so much?
Huh?
Sinai...
Please forgive me for not knowing.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know how you really felt.
I didn't understand the significance.
Please...
Forgive me for being ignorant.
I don't care.
It's okay.
I at least knew that it wasn't really okay.
I knew that, but...
It didn't stop me.
Why not?
Is it because you feel sorry for me?
I'm kidding.
I won't be needy.
Sinai...
I can't see your face.
Not out here like this.
It's too dark.
It's just all too dark.
The rain.
I never noticed any of the signs before.
Yes.
None at all.
Not until it started.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
Of course I am.
Why is that?
Is it because I'm a girl?
That's not it.
It's because you're...
Because you're my friend.
Well, isn't this...
What you do with all your friends?
Because you do this with Mugi, too.
Right?
Oh, no.
I did that.
She's about to cry.
I'm making her cry.
Tell me if you don't want to do this, okay?
I won't.
And why not?
Because I really...
care about you.
I know.
You care about me as a friend.
I know that I'm someone special to you.
You can't say no to me.
Because you don't want to lose me, too.
So, of course,
I'm going to take advantage
for all the cruel things you've done to me in the past.
And especially if you're never able to fall in love with me,
then I will take whatever I can get,
even if it's just your warmth.
And do the same to me.
Give me this.
I love you.
I wonder what he would have said if I told him.
I have loved you for a very long time.
Thank you.
It started.
Actually.
Just another one of my fantasies.
A future that will never be.
Brother.
These lips feel so soft.
And smell so sweet.
This isn't working.
No matter how hard I imagine,
I just see the girl I know.
Hanabi.
Sanai.
Tell me what you want me to do.
Let me hear it.
Please.
Wait.
No, I can't.
Or is it you want me to stop?
If you don't like this,
I can quit.
You're weak to things that feel good, huh?
I'm not.
It's because when you put your hand all the way down there,
it just feels so good.
That's why.
Yeah.
That's because.
I love you so much, Hanabi.
That's why.
You can sense I'm touching someone that I really care about.
That's why it feels so good.
Don't you see?
That's what love feels like.
I want you to be filled with me.
It's not that I didn't know already.
That there's always a limit.
There's only so much passion one can give.
And I filled my void with Sinai.
I used all of that up.
And now I'm sitting somewhere cold in my head.
All alone.
Geez.
I guess you can't go back to being just friends with Sinai now.
This is your fault again.
You know that, don't you?
Today was the first day you took advantage of someone's true feelings.
You're no different than that woman.
The hussy that stole our brother away from us.
You're both scum!
I know that already.
I'm aware of it.
I'm no match.
Not for that woman at least.
She's already gone and realized how much I feel about brother.
And she's purposefully trying to hurt me for it.
I can feel it.
It's painfully obvious.
Her smug sense of dominance over me as a woman.
But if I'm no match for her now, I soon will be.
It's time to change.
However I have to.
Tell me, which causes you the most pain?
Mugi?
Or Mr. Kanai?
I see, then.
So you know how Mugi feels about you, too.
So then, let me guess here.
Since he has no chance with the person he pines for,
he's just filling the void with some accessible classmate.
This bitch!
Yes, of course it's me.
I'm the one both are in love with.
Is it really all that much fun for you
to be loved by people you don't even like?
What?
Why not?
Being desired by men and taking them away from someone.
There's no greater
feeling in the world.
I'll be asked if I could.
I just如何 to avoid my work.
I'm sorry.
I just temin' back to the end.
I can't stop all my strength.
I think it's like,
not another word.
It looks pretty
good.
I'm hoping
if I could.
Give it a bow back
and I'll try.
So
,
how about
you
I'm